<idea-plugin>
  <id>com.shetline.ligatures-limited</id>
  <name>Ligatures Limited</name>
  <vendor email="kerry@shetline.com" url="https://github.com/kshetline/ligatures-limited-intellij">Kerry Shetline</vendor>
  <description><![CDATA[
  <h3>Code ligatures <i>only where you want them</i>, not where you don't.</h3><br>

  <p><a href="https://github.com/kshetline/ligatures-limited-intellij#ligatures-limited">README page
    for <i>Ligatures Limited</i></a>, with full documentation.</p>
  <br>
  <p><i>Ligatures Limited</i> allows code ligatures, like those found in Fira Code and other fonts, to be
    rendered only where they make the most sense — typically as operators and punctuation, for example,
    <code>&lt;=</code> and <code>!=</code>. Everywhere else (using configurable rules) ligatures are
    suppressed, so they don't do weird things inside strings and comments and the like.</p>
  <br>
  <p>Ligatures are also suppressed at the current insert cursor position, making it easier to see what
    you're doing as you type. Optionally this can be done for all ligatures on the currently-edited line.</p>
  <br>
  <p>This plugin works automatically as soon as it is installed and enabled. See the control panel in
    Settings/Preferences → Editor → Ligatures Limited to change options and configuration. Also make
    sure in Settings/Preferences → Editor → Font that a ligature font has been selected, and
    “Enable font ligatures” is checked.</p>
  ]]></description>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <h2>1.0.8</h2>
      <ul><li>Extended the compatibility of this plugin back to late 2021 IDE releases (>=212.5712.43).</ul>
    <h2>1.0.7</h2>
      <ul>
         <li>Restored missing configuration UI broken in newer IDE versions by the relocation Json5Language.
         <li>Updated a deprecated method call.
      </ul>
    <h2>1.0.6</h2>
      <ul><li>Catch a color-related exception somewhere deep in GeneralHighlightingPass.</ul>
    <h2>1.0.5</h2>
      <ul><li>Fixed a null exception.</ul>
    <h2>1.0.4</h2>
      <ul><li>Fixed occasional exceptions thrown by disposed editors.</ul>
    <h2>1.0.3</h2>
      <ul><li>Fixed handling of cursor position when tab characters are used for indentation.</ul>
    <h2>1.0.2</h2>
      <ul><li>Fixed a bug where the extension would fail to start when currently available languages could not be checked.</ul>
    <h2>1.0.1</h2>
      <ul><li>Recognize as a ligature four or more dashes, by themselves, without a leading <b>&lt;</b> or trailing <b>&gt;</b>.</ul>
    <h2>1.0.0</h2>
      <ul><li>First stable release</ul>
  ]]></change-notes>

  <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.json</depends>

  <applicationListeners>
    <listener class="com.shetline.lligatures.LigaturesLimited" topic="com.intellij.ide.AppLifecycleListener"/>
  </applicationListeners>

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <applicationConfigurable instance="com.shetline.lligatures.LigaturesLimitedConfig"
                             groupId="editor" id="com.shetline.lligatures.LigaturesLimited"
                             displayName="Ligatures Limited"/>
    <applicationService serviceImplementation="com.shetline.lligatures.LigaturesLimitedSettings"/>
    <highlightVisitor implementation="com.shetline.lligatures.LigaturesLimited"/>
    <highlightingPassFactory implementation="com.shetline.lligatures.LigaturesLimited"/>
  </extensions>

  <actions>
  </actions>
</idea-plugin>
